[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "And do you think that he should be executed if he's found guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "I think he should get the exact amount of mercy he gave everyone in that theater.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Did you feel that in some way he was trying to cheat natural justice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "The man is a coward.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Has your view of the death penalty changed because of what happened in Aurora that day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "I think that in a society that is as violent as ours, we need a lot of different ways to control it and the death penalty is one.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Aurora"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Have you thought through what the additional torment of a trial, with all the details that may emerge about what happened, not just to your son but the others that lost their lives and were wounded would all come back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", ",", "RB", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I can only speak for myself and for my family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Are you any nearer having any kind of understanding why Holmes did what he did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "I have no interest in understanding him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Holmes"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "What is your view of the gun control debate in America right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "I watched the senator today on CNN and it seems like everybody wants to point fingers at everybody else and talked about filibustering.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "What do you say to those politician who say, well, I'd love to -- I'd love to vote for an assault weapons ban but it may cost me my job?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "WP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I say if you have to do your job by lying, you need to get another job.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Let me ask you first, Dana, we had a pretty civilized discussion today on your radio show, but when you hear a man like Tom Teves speak so eloquently and just desperate for something to happen, what do you say to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "It was absolutely heartbreaking.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana", "Tom Teves"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Colorado"]}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Do you really think in your heart that the correct response of a great nation like America to an appalling atrocity like Sandy Hook is to race to sell more guns, more ammunition, and to expand gun rights?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "RBR", "NN", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Well, first of all the murderer in Colorado who killed 12 people should be executed 12 times.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sandy Hook"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Now, when you hear those kind of statistics, I suppose the obvious question is this: Does a wrong conviction of somebody -- and we don't know whether someone being executed -- we have to presume, I would imagine that some may have been before this -- does that on its own not count enough for the desire to execute others?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "RB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "I think if we are going to have the conversation about whether or not the death penalty is a legitimate form of punishment, that's a conversation that folks can have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Look, there is a Second Amendment and it's important.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "So, finally, and very quickly, Grover Norquist, are you claiming responsibility for the president taking his eye off the ball?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "I think the sequester is responsible for the president not doing as well on basketball as he might.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Grover Norquist"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "And should they think about that going forward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "It's a great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Would you jump in a different way if you knew there was a big drop off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "You know, I think that this thing was just a fluke.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "What is your advice to him going forward in terms of rehabilitation, not just physically, but mentally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, I think, number one, he has to do his rehab because, you know, when you're young, and you get hurt, Piers, you try to always rush and come back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Have you become homophobic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Over I'd say less 10, 12 years, I've enjoyed such a degree of independence and freedom, I can basically do whatever I want.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Are you homophobic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Yes, on the -- on the surface it sounds really bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 463, "question": "What difference would that make?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "To me it's an important difference but I don't think we have time to go into it right now, when you read it in the transcript, which I'd gone back and created, I can do a couple of things to show you and highlight --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Are you somebody that objects to a gay lifestyle and to gay marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "If the question is asked to make things simple for the audience and I believe that it is, I'd like to make it even simpler.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "So you're not homophobic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "If you want to keep this simple for the audience, let me just give you a straight no, I'm not homophobic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Why didn't you know what you were talking about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Because the nature of spontaneous improvisation, I had done it a complete show as truth and then the audience requested reality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Are you -- with all the members of the gay community who are outraged by what you said, are you -- are you sorry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Yes, I am very much so because what's being questioned is my support for that community.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "And do you have any problem with gay marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Do you support it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "So you support full gay rights?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Michelle Shocked", "Michelle Shocked"]}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 521, "question": "What do you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "I mean that I have been diligently working for the last five years on a project that is if I have not managed to convince you that I have very much at stake in putting this question to rest is Michelle Shocked homophobic, does Michelle Shocked support the gay community --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "CC", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Do you feel to your satisfaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Well, you've answered them very clearly and people can make their own minds up if you mean it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]